

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Umm Algura University**

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering
- graduation in 06/2022

# CONTACT

- +966591488657
- mohammedbandah@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammed-bandah-1407a8172/
- Saudi Arabia

#### **SKILLS**

English

Analyzing Designing and programming

Passion for learning and eagerness

Writing report

## **CERTIFICATES**

- Google Add Realism to AR applications using ARCore Depth API
- Google Website without hosting
- Google Valuing financial technology: a technical view out of the hypo
- Google Introduction to Firefox by Google
- Cisco Cybersecurity
- CompTIA Security+
- CCNA-Cyberops

## **MOHAMMED BANDAH**

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm Mohammed Bandah, Computer Engineer committed to improving system design and operations for reliable workflow management. Researches and implements budget-conscious security and encryption solutions to protect user privacy and increase overall network health. I have a goal and passion to reach a high position in my field, improve my educational level, gain many experiences and public relations.

### **EXPERIENCE**

(Fanaredu, Mecca) software IT Jul 2022 - Oct 2022

- Web designer
- processing techniques
- Data processing

(Arbhaj Company, Mecca) Programs developer May 2022 - Jul 2022

- marafiq program development
- data analysis
- Office 365 programs

(Saudi airlines , jeddah) Cybersecurity Jun 2020 - Sep 2020

- computer security operations
- data protection
- Protect the system from hacking

(AL-YAMAMA , Mecca) Crowd organizer Aug 2018 - Sep 2018

- Organization and Management
- Writing daily reports